Three, two, one, cheese!
Okay, change your pose.
Ready.
One, two, three.
Looks great.
Shen Xi,
we're leaving.
We're heading out.
Shen Xi,
And you are...
I'm Gao Yayan.
I just presented the award to you.
Gao Yayan,
daughter of Gao Yuhai,
the heiress of Wending Group, right?
What?
You want back the few thousand in bonus
you gave me?
Take it back.
You don't need to be
so hostile towards me.
I've been following
the whole competition.
I know
this result is unfair to you.
Fair?
Gao Yuhai's daughter is talking
to me about fairness.
Isn't it ironic?
Sorry,
I have something to do. I gotta go.
I used to study dance too.
Before the entrance exam,
my dad wouldn't let me go.
I broke my ankle jumping off a building
and can never dance again.
So I understand you.
And in a way,
you're actually better off than me.
Can we talk?
That's all.
I completely lost the right to dance.
I went to study
business administration
and architectural engineering.
Your dad is such a
psycho.
I'm sorry.
Please don't mind me.
I just wanted to stand up for you.
You're telling the truth.
You didn't wrong him at all.
So I really envy you.
You can dance freely on stage.
This competition is nothing.
Your future has infinite possibilities.
T-Then what about you now?
Are you working at Wending Group?
I'm not going to work at his company.
Isn't he rich?
Doesn't he love controlling me?
Then I might as well take his money
and do what I like.
Do you still have
dreams about dancing now?
Or any wishes?
Of course I do.
Back then,
because of the art exam incident,
my dad held
this dance competition every year,
claiming it was to make it up to me.
He let me be a judge, a guest,
and the chief planner.
But so what?
None of this means anything.
Because I can't dance anymore,
and that's the truth.
But if you're talking about
my own wish,
I've always wanted to make a dance drama.
There's a little girl in this dance drama.
She's like a little bird, trying
hard
to fly.
But
her wings were cruelly broken
by her father.
You want to make
an autobiographical dance drama.
I guess you could say that.
If it's really possible,
right? Then
I might as well spend Gao Yuhai's money.
That's what I think.
Yayan,
I have a dance drama here.
It was written by a-a
friend of mine.
It's called "Circle".
Although it's not about your story,
I think
the emotion it wants to express
is the same.
I wonder
if you're interested.
Sure.
You can show it to me when you have time.
I'll call him over right now.
Actually,
a woman's intuition is quite accurate.
I was hesitating
whether to introduce
Gao Yayan to Song Yanfei.
For the sake of the dance drama,
the sooner, the better, of course.
But my intuition told me
something might happen
between them.
Didn't Gao Yayan know
he's your boyfriend?
Or
did she know
and just steal him openly?
That's on me.
When I called Song Yanfei,
he was disappointed to hear
I didn't get the bonus.
But he got excited
hearing Gao Yayan was willing to invest,
and came right over with the script.
Before he arrived,
I didn't have time
to explain our relationship.
They had a great chat that day
and basically confirmed
the collaboration on the spot.
On the way back,
Song Yanfei...
045 Song Yanfei
0451 Liang Yanfei
She just made one request.
That's great. That's great.
I knew we could do it.
Thanks to you,
Shen Xi.
This is great.
I really feel like "Circle"
will premiere soon.
Yayan is great.
But...
Her dad
is completely fine.
For rich families like hers,
hundreds of thousands
is just pocket money.
I know it too well.
I've been there.
It's just that there's one thing.
What?
We need to keep our relationship
a secret from Gao Yayan for now.
Why?
Are you going to use your looks
to seduce Gao Yayan?
That's not entirely out of the question.
Then go ahead.
I'm kidding.
How could I?
Just kidding. Just kidding.
I mean,
after the dance drama
premieres successfully,
we can tell her the truth
at the celebration party.
Wouldn't that be nice?
We shouldn't make her feel like
we're teaming up
to scheme for her money.
That would look so bad.
Are you serious?
Of course.
That's more like it.
Give me a kiss then.
Who wants to kiss you?
Song Yanfei, you...
Yanfei,
I just rearranged
the female solo dance part.
The moves are smoother now,
and the emotions are better expressed.
Come on.
Let me show you.
Shen Xi,
what's wrong?
Let's break up.
So you agreed to break up?
What else could I do?
Could I keep him
or his heart?
I didn't argue with him.
I just made one request.
On the day of the premiere,
I must be the one to dance this role.
Consider it a perfect ending
to our relationship
and all these years of hard work.
But there's one thing I don't get.
Why did you wear a mask
and have Bai Sha cover for you?
Because I hit and killed Gao Yuhai.
So
you mean
I can't be the lead dancer anymore?
I'm sorry.
After all, that's her dad.
And you...
But I thought of a way.
You might have to compromise a bit
and wear a mask.
Wear a mask?
I'll arrange for someone
to take your place.
There's a formation
where a group stands together.
I'll pull her out
and let you dance in her spot.
You can do your lifts
and other moves normally.
It's basically like you're still the lead.
Because you know
Xingchen is my best friend.
He's in charge of investigating
your traffic accident.
If he finds out you're performing
and knows about us,
and discovers
you're close to Yayan...
I'm afraid he'll overthink it.
Less trouble is better.
What do you think?
All right.
Let's do as you say.
I'm sorry for putting you through this.
Let's eat.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Captain Li,
about my car...
Bai Xiaosi is suspected
of driving without a license
and evading inspection.
We are dealing with it.
Also, I need to remind you
that you cannot leave Checheng
until you receive our official notice.
If this happens again,
it won't be resolved so easily.
Understood?
I can't hide from you anyway.
I'll wait for your notice then.
Okay.
Get some rest.
Let's go.
Bye.
Wei,
please have someone keep an eye on them.
No problem.
Hey,
are you asleep?
I want to see you.
Here, Officer Jiang.
Try the coffee I ground myself.
Thanks.
Yayan brought these coffee beans
back from Africa.
It's really good.
I really didn't expect
her to tell you everything.
Do you have anything to add?
Nothing to add.
It's just...
what happened back then
dragged you down.
For all these years,
I've been looking for a chance
to apologize to you in person.
But I just couldn't find the right
opportunity.
It's in the past.
About what happened back then...
Professionally,
as a cop,
I failed my duty.
Personally,
we grew up
together, and
I really failed
to take good care of your dad.
That's why I quit being a detective.
You two childhood friends...
Now that everything is out in the open,
there are no more issues,
right?
Let's toast with coffee
to celebrate you two burying the hatchet
and making up.
Cheers.
Why are you everywhere?
Not bad.
Xingchen, your buddy here
is quite something.
He's handsome,
and has both high EQ and IQ.
My childhood friend
has always been outstanding.
You two make a really good team.
I wish you a smooth partnership
and a happy marriage.
Stop messing around.
Enough with the nonsense.
Seriously though,
are you sure there's nothing else to add?
Actually, there is.
When
Yayan and I first got together,
the dance drama had actually
already taken shape.
But
when her dad found out we were together,
he absolutely disapproved.
The dance drama needed funding
at the time,
and Yayan had no other choice
but to go on a blind date
with a guy her dad arranged.
Feng Shu.
Right, the one who framed me.
Later, Yayan made a huge scene
at her dad's funeral
to keep her power in the company
and kick Feng Shu out.
Rich family drama.
It's like a TV show coming to life.
Something like that.
Later I realized
Yayan is much more forgiving
than I thought.
My causing a scene at the premiere
was really unnecessary.
So,
she knows everything
about Shen Xi?
Yes.
I've known for a long time
that Shen Xi is his ex-girlfriend.
I also know
she sacrificed a lot
for this dance drama.
So I can understand
why she can't let it go.
Yanfei explained all this to me clearly
after the three of us first met.
The script and the concept
are both excellent.
Coupled with Director Song's
personal experience,
I believe
this will definitely be a blockbuster.
Thank you, Ms. Gao.
We definitely won't let
your money go to waste.
Yes, thank you.
It's not my money.
And please don't call me Ms. Gao.
It sounds like you're calling my dad.
Just call me Yayan or Yanyan.
Are you two a couple?
No.
Everyone says that.
We're good bros.
Pure bros.
Don't listen to his nonsense.
We're not bros.
We're
besties.
He is
a pure sister.
Yes, pure sisters.
I can tell.
You two truly love each other.
Of course.
And when we were creating
the dance drama later,
many of our ideas were
surprisingly identical.
Still writing...
Thanks.
Look, Yayan.
This is a new character I wrote,
a little girl.
Throughout the play,
she just stands high up on the stage
in a corner,
looking down.
People from all circles pass by her,
yet she doesn't belong to any of them.
Do you know
what she represents?
She represents innate resources,
having powerful backing,
and reaping what others sow.
Oh my god,
you get me so well!
How do you understand me so well?
Seriously,
I used to
discuss scripts with Shen Xi too.
What she liked were
the characters in my scripts.
She liked the pink dresses
and dazzling lights.
She fantasized about
the glamour of standing on stage.
But you're different.
You understand the helplessness
and sorrow in my scripts,
and you can see
the souls of the characters.
We resonate with each other a lot.
I really didn't expect this.
I didn't expect someone
to understand me so well.
Starring
Li Xingchen, Yu Xiaotong
Shen Xi, Xie Tiantian
Special Appearance
Feng Shu, Liu Yakun
Bai Xiaosi, Liu Xiaolong (Liu Xubai)
Bai Jiuzhou, Qin Peng
Forensic Doctor Cheng Gong
Young Li Xingchen, Li Yuanche
Chen Nuoyan
Lead Singer Xu Weina
Xiao Ze's Father He
Xiao Ze's Mother Zhao Yue'en
Hong Zhifeng
Assistant Bai Zhihao
Hu Wenshu
Li Ziying
Woman Sun Meili
Girl Yingying Huang Mingfei
Nanny Wang Chunyang
Shareholders Huang Xinyang, Wang Wentao
Xia Youzhen
Gao Yuhai's Secretary Dudu
Fleeing Driver Liu Haohan
Drivers Wang Yiguo, Liang Hui
Waiters Liu Jiaqi, Dai Guoming
Mother Liu Li
Daughter Zhang Qiying
Driver Old Zhao Wei Hong
College Students Zhang Ang, Wu Yingxue
Locksmith Fu Wang
Surveillance Police Qin Zhiqiang
Xiao Ze's Mother Pei Xiao
Stagehand Little Zhang Li
Young Man Tang Yuye
Police Colleague Li Lijun
Scrap Yard Boss Zhang Li Chenghu
Company Head Bai Yongjun
Mother Zhang Minghui
Woman Liu Yutong
Man in Black Zhu Yiqi
Bai Xiaosi's Stunt Double Zhao Peng
Policewoman Wu Lihua
Execution Doctor Sister Geng
Actor Hu Zexuan
Receptionist
Hot Pot Restaurant Boss Qin Haitao
Chief Presenter Xu Yue
Co-Presenters Feng Fei, Guo Zhiyuan
Chief Planner Li Meina
Chief Distributor Hu Kaichen
Police Consultant/Original Story Fu Jun
Production Team
Producers Sui Sanlong, Li Xin
Production Manager Liu Zhilong
On-Site Producer Hu Huazheng
Coordinator Liu Xinyu
Stagehand Team
Stagehands Xu Ganggang, Zhao Menglin
Yang Qunbao
Kitchen
Vegetable Washer Hu Xiuxia
Driver Team
Li Zhiwei, Ma Yuan
Wang Ji, Zhang Xiong
Zhang Kai, Liang Hui
Wang Yiguo
Hu Lei, Qiao Xueyue
Zhang Haiping, Cao Yongjie
Yue Shunming
Executive Director Sui
Script Supervisor Li Ting
Casting Coordinator Kang Hai
On-Site Assistant Director Liu Haohan
IT Jin Linxin
Sound Team
Sound Assistants: Wu Yingxue, Zhang Qichun
Art and Props Department
Production Designer: Zhao Daqian
Assistant Art Director: Wang Tianyi
Props Master: Sun Donghua
On-Set Assistant: Li Yao
Director of Photography: Li Yixu
A Camera Focus Puller: Yao Yonglei
A Camera Assistant: Li Xinghan
B Camera Focus Puller: Li Chenlong
B Camera Assistant
C Camera Focus Puller: Xie Xiaozhong
Aerial Cinematographer: Zhan Yuchen
Still Photographer: Dong Guiping
Lighting Department
Lighting Assistants: Zhang Xiaoguang,
Chang Lin
Te Rigun
Wardrobe and Makeup Supervisor: Ma
On-Set Hair and Makeup: Liu Lu, Guo Xinye
Beijing Very Cola Culture Media Co., Ltd.
Marketing Director: Li Yiyi
Media Manager: Yue Yue
Project Coordinator: Zhao Zihan
Graphic Designers: Ren Zhongjun, Shi Qi
Post-Production
Post-Production Coordinator: Zhang
Opening Titles: Gao Dong
Trailer Production: Li Xin
Subtitles: Su
Dialogue Editor: Dong Xuebing
Ambience Editor: Zhang Xinyu
Beijing Wenhui Qiming Culture
Communication Co., Ltd.
Post-Production Supervisor: Gao Dong
Su, Li
Music Production
Hong Kong, China Musical Theatre
Score Production: Xiao Zhuang, Wang Dafu
Liu Zining
Score Mixing: Zhao Yi
Song Recording Studio:
Beijing Landuo Recording Studio
Songs
Lyrics: Yue Shun
Composer: Xiao Zhuang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Song of Spring"
Vocals: Zhang Keying
Children's Vocals: Zhang Maolin
Lyrics: Yue Shunming
Arranger: Xiao
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Lyrics: Bai Yuxiang
Composer: Xiao Zhuang
Vocals: Ben Damiao
Gao Jingman
Composer: Xu Yue
"That's All"
Gao Jingman
Composer: Xu Yue
Producer: Xu Yue
"Half a Beat"
Vocals: Xu Yue
Composer: Xu Yue
Arranger: @/non_ay
Wang Weijia
Lyrics: Bai Yuxiang
Arranger: Zhao Yi
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
"Only You" (Russian)
Lyrics: Bai Yuxiang
Xiao Zhuang
Producer: Xiao Zhuang
Publicity Department
of Shiyan Municipal Party Committee
Shiyan Public Security Bureau
Shiyan Dongfeng Hometown Historical
Materials Exhibition Hall
Shiyan Xiaowujia Restaurant
Shiyan Hengjiu Kanghua Real Estate
Co., Ltd. (Longcheng Mansion)
Sunshine Dance Art Training School,
Maojian District, Shiyan
Meiyijia Convenience Store, No. 88
Gongyuan Road, Zhangwan District, Shiyan
Exclusive Social Media Platform
Chief Partner Media
Sichuan Jiaodian Pictures Co., Ltd.
Sichuan Prism Chuangjie Film
and Television Culture Co., Ltd.
Qinghe (Beijing) Culture Media Co., Ltd.